《纸牌屋》前情提要...
Previously on House of Cards...
如果明天有人朝我开枪  那绝不会是意外
If a bullet comes my way tomorrow, it will not be an accident,
而且我得赶快躲开
and I must be quick to duck.
你知道格兰特将军是如何击败李将军的吗
Do you know how Grant defeated Lee?
他的人更多
He had more men.
而且他愿意让他们去送死
And he was willing to let them die.
是屠杀  而非策略  赢得了战争
It was butchery, not strategy, which won the war.
你以前酗酒  是吗
You used to be an alcoholic, correct?
-酒瘾是戒不掉的    -你怀念这味道吗
- Not "used to be."   - Do you miss it?
你们两个都让我很失望
You've both disappointed me greatly.
雷蒙德  你还在吗
Raymond, are you still there?
这是他20年来第一次挂掉我电话
That's the first time he's ever hung up on me.
我真为你难过
I feel for you.
我刚跟一个叫赛斯·格雷森的人通了电话
I just got off the phone with a guy named Seth Grayson.
马博利医生有没有为克莱尔·安德伍德做过堕胎
Did Dr. Marbury perform an abortion for Claire Underwood?
他有一本日记
He kept a journal.
这日记就是我的简历
That journal is my version of a resume.
会成功的
This is gonna work.
我没选择了  但你还有
I don't have a choice, but you still do.
你想进去看看  是吧
You wanted to see inside one, right?
务必做得干净利落  道格 一击致命
This needs to be clean, Doug. One fall of the ax.
-趴在地上    -立刻趴下
- On the ground.   - On the ground now!
现在  杀戮开始
And the butchery begins.
我们现在面临能源危机  弗兰克
We've got an energy crisis, Frank.
白宫应该...
Now what the White House needs to --
总统选择对中国保持强硬态度
The president chose to remain tough on China.
不  那是被你逼的
No. You forced him to.
你选择了冯  是你让我和他见面的
You chose Feng. You're the one who put me in a room with him.
厨子手艺不好
The cook can't blame his ingredients
不能去怪原料差
if he doesn't like how they taste together.
如果钐的价格不降
If Samarium prices don't reduce,
市场只能随之上调电价
the market will have no choice but to compensate.
那样对每一个使用空调的人来说都是坏消息
That's bad for everyone who owns an air conditioner.
你应该去找总统本人谈谈
You should speak to the president himself.
总统最近不是很重视我的意见
the president hasn't placed much value on my advice lately.
我和你一样  雷蒙德
I'm in the same boat as you, Raymond.
是啊
Yeah.
不同的是  你和他的办公室只隔三道门
Difference being you've got an office three doors down from the Oval.
我们同心协力吧
Let's work together, for Christ sakes.
只要你愿意  我可以忘记斯波特瑟尔维尼亚的事
I'm wiling to put Spotsylvania behind us if you are.
正合我意
I want nothing more.
那你会去跟他谈
Then you'll talk to him?
我开会要迟到了  雷蒙德
Look, I'm late for a meeting, Raymond.
答应还是不答应  弗兰克
Yes or no, Frank?
我不能保证他听得进去
I can't guarantee he'll listen.
这不是答应
That's not a yes.
总比不答应强
But it's better than a no.
称职的拳击手都能看出对手什么时候不行了
Any pugilist worth his salt knows when someone's on the ropes,
这时候就该果断连续出拳
that's when you throw a combination to the gut
左勾拳直击下颚
and a left hook to the jaw.
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
翻译 卢克·天意   somehacker   小饭
翻译 卫老哥   某豚   肉松   冬麟   木月
蓝光版调整  timhal@HDWinG字幕组   后期 饿得慌
顾问 老杜   校对 草草   总监 草草
本字幕由YYETS翻译 HDWinG字幕组修正 请勿去掉制作者信息
《纸牌屋》
第二季  第六集
钐的价格他们绝不会让步
Samarium is the last thing they'll let go of.
只要能源价格一直涨  他们就有谈判筹码
As long as our energy prices rise, they have the leverage.
如果我们只是静观其变呢  跟他们比瞪眼
Why don't we offer nothing? Move toward attrition.
如果中国不参加再融资债券拍卖
If China doesn't show at the refunding auction,
长期利率会一路飙升
long-term interest rates will spike.
一个星期后我们的十年期国债
And in a week yields on our 10-year notes
将突破7%大关
will pierce the seven-percent threshold.
那是有可能
That could happen.
但如果我们现在妥协  那就是必然了
But if we go soft now, that will happen.
你说我们应该强硬一些
You mean go on the offensive.
至少应该考虑一下
We should at least consider it.
中国人不吃敬酒  我们就上罚酒
The Chinese don't like carrots. Let's see how they like the stick.
怎么做
Well, what might that look like?
增加粮食检查的频率
We could raise inspection rates on foodstuffs.
把他们的粮食扣在港口直到腐烂
Hold them in our ports till they rot.
提高多少
How much of a raise?
想要有效果要提高20%
20% if we want to draw blood.
用增加抽查次数的方式进行掩饰
Bury the move with increased spot checks all the way around.
这类措施不能解决眼前的问题
These sort of tactics don't solve the immediate problem.
人们现在交着三倍的电费
People are paying triple the standard rate for electric.
到八月份  就是五倍
We'll hit a five-fold increase by August.
如果你  总统先生  通过行政命令
What if you, Mr. President, by executive order,
从第三方手里购买钐呢
purchase Samarium through a third party?
绕过中国
Cut the Chinese out.
迫使他们提高全球价格
Force them to either raise their prices worldwide
或是降低价格维持跟我们的交易
or lower them to keep direct flow with us.
当然  对外宣称是为了国防需要进行钐储备
We stockpile Samarium for denfense purposes, of course,
然后悄悄的把多余的钐卖给我们核能源方面的盟友
And quietly sell what we don't need to our friends in nuclear energy.
以优惠价格
At a discount.
核能源补助
A subsidy for nuclear power?
有钱人相互接济  这别人会怎么看啊
The richest of the rich? How's that gonna play?
我们正在面对国家危机
We're dealing with a national crisis.
我们不能受公众舆论的影响
We can't get sidetracked with public opinion.
这能让中国知道我们愿意耐心等待
It would show China we're willing to wait this out.
我们有这份钱吗
Do we have the resources?
我要计算一下
I'd have to run the numbers,
预期波动  考虑不同模式
anticipate fluctuations, consider different models --
估计一下
Your best guess.
有  可以进行中度储备
We do. For a moderate stockpile.
那好  以国防部名义起草请求
All right. Draw up a request from the Defense Department.
-是  先生    -琳达  起草行政命令
- Yes, sir.    - Linda, draft the executive order.
凯茜  确保我们能找到一个第三方
And Cathy, make sure we have a third-party conduit
购买钐
to purchase the Samarium.
跟印度买吧
We'll go through India.
那巴基斯坦可要不高兴了
Well, that won't fly well with Pakistan.
我会提前告知他们  只要及时告知他们
I'll alert them in advance. As long as they're in the loop,
就没什么问题  我们又不欠他们什么
we'll be all right. Not that we owe them any favors.
那好  开始工作吧
All right. Let's get to work.
贝茜  还加上E条款下的三条罪名
Come on, Betsy. Three additional counts under Section E?
三条已经很少了  反映了对犯罪意图的狭义解释
Three is low. It reflects a narrow interpretation of criminal intent.
你的委托人入侵了数据中心
Your client broke into a data center.
你能提供什么
What's the offer?
我不会认罪的
I'm not doing a plea.
让我来处理这个
Let me handle this.
他们不想开庭审判
They don't want a trial.
我能在公开法庭上高声提出的问题
The questions I'll be raising loud and clear in open court...
卢卡斯  别这样
Lucas, please.
我们也有问题  古德温先生
We have our own questions, Mr. Goodwin.
比如  你怎么会有这些
For example, what were you doing with these?
这不是我拍的
I didn't take these.
是在你公寓发现的
They were in your apartment.
安德伍德拍的
Underwood took them.
你觉得陪审团能信吗
Do you really expect a jury to believe that?
是他  他们有一腿
He did. They were having an affair --
他们只会如实看待这些证据
Or are they gonna see them for what they are?
你迷恋巴恩斯女士
Proof of our obsession with Ms. Barnes
还编出一套荒唐的阴谋论
and the ludicrous conspiracy you have concocted
来解释她的死
to explain her death.
你们什么条件
Tell us what you're offering.
你委托人供认以下罪名  E条款下一条
Your client pleads to one count under Section E
闯入数据中心
for breaking into a data center,
欺诈一条  偷《先驱报》的密码
one count for fraud, for stealing the password from the Herald.
第一项获罪10年  第二项10年  同时计算
10 years under Section E. 10 years for fraud. Served concurrently.
服刑7年可假释
Eligible for parole in seven.
我想单独跟委托人谈
I'd like to speak to my client, alone.
请关掉录像录音设备
Cameras and recording equipment off, please.
我介绍总统  他来介绍你
I'll introduce the president, then he'll introduce you.
如果他在  就不能点名军方
If he's there, we can't mention the military.
只能说全国皆有这种现象
Just the endemic problem nationwide.
当然  我理解
Of course. I understand.
很好  那再过一遍讲词
Good. So we should go through these speeches
看还有没有...
and make sure that there's nothing --
你好  安德伍德夫人
Hi, Mrs. Underwood.
你好  克里斯蒂娜
Hello, Christina.
沃克夫人  你找我
Mrs. Walker, you asked for me?
我们要确认一下总统能不能
We need to confirm whether the president's going
去新奥尔良
to make it to New Orleans.
是这周五吧
This Friday, correct?
是  但我知道他今早有内阁会议
Yes. But I know he had a cabinet meeting this morning,
所以我想
so I imagine...
我这就去和琳达沟通一下
I'll talk to Linda right away.
谢谢
Thanks.
我知道你希望加勒特去  可能源危机的事
I know you want Garrett there. But with this energy crisis...
不是那个
No. It's not that.
什么
What?
我不该说的
I shouldn't say anything.
这下你非说不可了
Well, now you have to tell me.
我就是向来不太喜欢克里斯蒂娜
I've just never been very fond of her. Christina.
为什么
Why not?
彼得·罗素
Peter Russo.
我就是不太喜欢跟老板上床的女人
I just have a thing about women who sleep with their bosses.
不过我相信他们是真心相爱
Anyway, I'm sure whatever they had was genuine.
也不关我事  只要她工作做得好
It's none of my business, 'cause if she's doing a good job,
其他也无所谓
that's all that matters, right?
加勒特还挺满意
Garrett seems to think she is.
那我就不多嘴了
Then I should just keep my feelings to myself.
如果总统不能去
So if the president is not able to be there,
对咱们或许也是好事
that could be a silver lining for us.
不用给军方留面子了
We won't have to hold back with the military.
电话监听  视频监控  预谋犯罪
Phone taps. Video surveillance. Premeditation.
长期动机  你没希望的
Sustained intent. They've got you cold.
如果我认罪  就没人知道真相了
If I plead out, that's it. No one hears the truth.
你不认罪的话  根本没人会听你的
If you don't plead, no one will hear you, period.
一直到你七八十岁
Not until you're in your 70s.
你和汉默施密特谈了吗
Have you talked to Hammerschmidt yet?
你没资格谈条件
You're in no position to make demands.
你说了又不算
It's not up to you.
你只会惹恼他们
All you'll do is piss them off.
听我说
Look,
这个交易很好
we've got a good deal here.
考虑到你的行为  算很不错了
A great deal, considering what you did.
趁他们没改主意  赶紧接受
You should take it before their change their mind.
汤姆·汉默施密特  我要跟他谈  否则就上法庭
Tom Hammerschmidt. I talk to him, or we're going to trial.
请抬起胳膊
Raise your arms, please.
这里有什么物品
You have something here?
项链
My neck chain.
请掏出来
May I see it?
真的吗  我还得解领带
Really? I gotta take off my tie.
必须看一下  先生
I need to see it, sir.
虔诚的基督徒啊  雷米
You're a good Christian, Remy.
我母亲的  是她虔诚
My mother's. She was the good Christian.
那你也是个好儿子
Well, then you're just the good son.
谢谢
Thank you, sir.
外面热吧
Hot out there, huh?
96华氏度  车里显示的
96, according to my car.
以前在加夫尼也这么热
We had heat like that back in Gaffney,
那会儿还没有空调
but we didn't know what air conditioning was,
我们认为夏天就该这么难熬
so we just accepted as fact that summer was meant to be miserable.
加不加水
Neat or with water?
只要水  不要酒
Just the water. You can hold the bourbon.
得找个解决办法
We need to find a solution
好让这个夏天美国人民不那么难熬
so that this one isn't miserable for 300 million people.
我有办法了
I already have found a solution.
得了吧  弗兰克  钐补助吗
Oh, please, Frank. A Samarium subsidy?
是你还是雷蒙德表示怀疑
Is that your skepticism or Raymond's?
我  估计他也是
Mine. Anticipating his.
你俩还没谈过
So you haven't spoken to him yet.
我想向他提出他会同意的条件
I want to offer him something he can agree to.
他没什么选择
Well, he doesn't have much of a choice.
你为什么要把他逼入绝境
Why are you cornering him?
我把价钱减半  这是在帮他啊
I'm cutting the rate by half. I'd call that liberating him.
你知道他可不这么看
You know that's not how he'll see it.
这场贸易战让北京方面
This trade war is preventing the refinery
迟迟不批准精炼厂项目
from being approved in Beijing.
目前  他跟冯的合资项目不是最重要的
His co-venture with Feng is not our highest priority right now.
稀土精炼厂能一劳永逸地解决这场危机
A rare earth refinery solves this crisis permanently.
那是三年之后了  这个夏天还是难熬
Three years from now. Not this summer.
不止如此  实施核能补助他至多不赔不赚
It's not just that. With the subsidy he'll break even at best,
那叫做生意吗
there's no point in doing business to hover between red and black.
雷蒙德的利益对我来说比他的合资项目更不重要
Raymond's profits are an even lower priority to me than his co-venture.
告诉我你的目的  弗兰克
Tell me what you're up to, Frank.
你跟塔斯克叫劲又得不到什么
There's nothing to gain by locking horn with Tusk.
问你的客户去  是塔斯克在叫劲
Ask your client. It's Tusk who's locking the horns.
他不喜欢矛盾
He's not a man who likes conflict.
我也不喜欢
Neither am I.
那就提出要求吧  我知道你不在乎核能补助
Then make the ask. 'Cause I know you don't care about the subsidy.
你有更大的目标
This is about something bigger.
我是个虔诚的基督徒  雷米  跟你母亲一样
I'm a good Christian, Remy, like your mother.
如果我想要别的  我会如实说的
I would tell you the truth if I wanted more.
你这是在发出信号吗
You trying to send a message?
也许吧
Perhaps.
那内容是什么
Which is?
顽固比顺从的代价更大
That stubbornness is far more costly than obedience.
谢谢你的水
Thanks for the water.
你站错队了  雷米
You're on the wrong side, Remy.
是啊  我们中肯定有一人站错
Yeah, well, one of us sure is.
大黄蜂飞回家后
And when the bumblebee flew home,
发现它的朋友们都抱着大桶蜂蜜在等他
all his friends were waiting with buckets honey, right?
他的朋友有蠕虫  老鼠
And he's got his worm friend and his mouse friend
蜘蛛和蜗牛
and his spider friend and his snail friend.
它们都有许多蜂蜜  他看上去开心多了  是吗
And they all had tons of honey. And he looks happier now, right?
-是啊    -是吗
- Yeah!   - Yeah?
于是他们开心地嗡嗡叫了起来
And so they all buzzzzed with happiness.
因为你和朋友们在一起  生活会甜蜜得多
Because life is sweet when you spend it with your friend.
对吗
Right?
你们会振动翅膀发出嗡鸣声吗  扇动小翅膀吧
Can you all buzz your wings? Buzz your little wings.
-我觉得会发出颤动的声音  就像    -就像
- I think it would make a fluttering noise, like...   - like
我不知道
I don't know.
你的颤动呢
Your flutters?
外面太热了  你不该抛球  弗兰西斯
It's too hot out here for you to be doing this, Francis.
我一直在喝水
I'm keeping hydrated.
这距离满足规定吗
Is that even regulation?
只到一半
It's only half.
但我不想让媒体看到我在大街上练习
But I don't want the press to see practicing on the street.
还记得你在格林维尔开球那次吗
You remember when you threw out that first pitch in Greenville?
我还在想你什么时候会提到那事呢
I was wondering how long it was gonna take you to bring that up.
那次还不是全国电视台直播呢
That wasn't even on national television.
祝你好运
Good luck.
谢谢
Thank you.
格林维尔发生了什么
What happened in Greenville?
格林维尔驱动队
The Greenville Drive.
红袜队的1A队
Single A team for the Red Sox.
主场作战  我站在投球区土墩上
It was a home game. I get on the mound.
你从土墩上抛球吗
You threw from the mound?
我想投个好球
Well, I wanted to throw a real pitch.
没抛好吗
Didn't make it.
差得远呢
Not even close.
一半吗
Halfway?
球在我松手前滑了出去
Ball slipped out of my hand just before I released it.
直线抛上了天
Went straight up in the air.
掉下来砸在我头上  全场爆发大笑
Hit me on top of the head. The whole stadium burst a gut laughing.
喜剧性投球
Comic relief pitcher.
真会说话  密查姆
That's very clever, Meechum.
别告诉克莱尔
Don't tell Claire.
我听到了
I heard that.
你跟他们处的真好
You're really good with them.
他们作手指画时  你看到罗比了吗
Did you see Robbie when they were finger-painting?
他脱掉了裤子  把他自己涂成蓝色
He pulled down his pants and started painting himself blue.
-没看到    -真的
- No.   - Yeah.
但愿我都洗干净了
Hope I got it all off.
艾利克斯和达利尔不会在意的
I'm sure Alex and Daria don't care.
他们总是让他光着身子四处跑
They let him run around naked all the time.
是啊  但不会像光屁股的蓝精灵
Yeah, but probably not with his Smurf ass.
我们今晚吃什么
What do we want to do for dinner tonight?
我还有一些吃剩的鸡肉  或者我们可以叫披萨
I've got some leftover chicken. Or we could order pizza.
披萨  不做菜
Pizza. No dishes.
是啊
Yeah.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我完全忘了有个朋友今晚要来接我
I -- I totally forgot I've got a friend picking me up tonight.
我完全忘了
I -- I completely blanked.
-没事    -我真的很抱歉
- That's fine.   - I'm really sorry.
不必道歉  是你男朋友吗
Don't sweat it. Is it, uh, your boyfriend?
不是  只是一个老朋友
No, no. Um, just an old friend.
我能见见他吗
Can I meet him?
他有点害羞  我不知道他是否愿意
he's kinda shy. I do-- I don't know if he'd be up for --
没事  没关系
Totally cool. Don't worry about it.
我们改天再一起吃晚饭
We'll just do dinner another night.
明天见
I'll see you tomorrow.
好  你知道去哪里找我
Yeah. You know where I'll be.
多久了
How long?
几个月了
Couple of months.
为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
我不能去教堂吗
I can't go to church?
你跟任何人有接触都可能暴露我们
Anywhere you interact with other people opens us up to risk.
那我就该整天闷在呼叫中心
Right. I'm just supposed to slave away at the fucking call center
或是待在公寓里不出来吗
and then lock myself in the apartment.
别这么小题大做
Don't get dramatic.
我喜欢这些人
I like the fellowship.
好吗  没有什么可担心的
Okay? There -- there's nothing to worry about there.
如果谁林奇堡的亲戚来访就能毁了一切
All it takes is one person's cousin to visit from Lynchburg.
或许是你的高中同学
Someone you went to high school with
或许是曾跟你共度良宵的客户
or some client that you spend the night with.
那些人才不会出现在这里
Those guys would never end up here.
你怎么知道
You don't know that.
我就是知道
Yeah. I do.
你不就跑来这里了吗
You ended up here, didn't you?
我不能这么生活
I can't live like this.
什么
What?
我不能这么生活
I can't live like this.
不  你能  你是个坚强的姑娘
Yes, you can. You're a strong girl.
就这些  这就是全部了吗
That's it? That's everything?
我知道  你以前就听过了
I know. You've heard it before.
作为一个朋友  卢卡斯  而不是记者
As a friend, Lucas. Not as a reporter.
我会接着挖
Now I dig.
我去打电话  去跑腿
I make the phone calls. I do the legwork.
他们对你还好吗
They treating you okay?
还行
It's fine.
我不是问那个
That's not what I asked.
他们非常想达成认罪协议
They're pushing the plea deal pretty hard.
你在认真考虑吗
How seriously are you considering it?
我想看看文章的影响
I want to see how this article impacts things.
你的律师怎么说
What does your lawyer say?
他觉得这是个坏主意  我应该认罪
He thinks that's a bad idea. That I should take the plea.
也许你应该听他的
Maybe you should listen to him.
不  我要文章  我确定
No. I want the article. That I'm certain of.
好吧  那我得赶快开始了
All right. I better get to it then.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你要知道
You need to know,
我会像对待其他报道一样对待这件事
I'm gonna treat this the way I would any other story.
报道事实  你也许不会喜欢我写的东西
Whatever the facts bear. You might not like what I write.
我明白
I get that.
我会先让你看  然后你再做决定
I'll let you read it first. Then you can decide.
我就是这意思
That's all I'm asking.
挺住
Hang in there.
能帮我擦掉吗  求你了
Can you wipe this off? Please?
其他核供应商都赞同吗
And the other nuclear providers are on board?
大部分  除了雷蒙德的公司
Most. Except Raymond's company.
还有几个
Couple of others.
湖港核电站  狼泉集团
Lakeport Nuclear. Wolf Springs.
我无法证明  但我敢肯定他们是串通好的
Now, I can't prove it, but I am absolutely sure they're colluding.
雷蒙德想让我丢脸
Raymond wants to embarrass me.
我提出方案  核能说客却不肯合作
I offer a solution, nuclear lobby turns its back.
他有拒绝的权利  总统先生
He has the right to refuse, Mr. President.
但他没法操纵能源市场
What he cannot do is manipulate the energy market.
你想对经销方施压
You want to put pressure on the distribution side.
不仅施压  彻底禁止纵向合并
More than pressure. Ban vertical integration entirely.
我们没有那个管制权力
We don't have that regulatory power.
我们给《紧急能源法案》加一条反垄断协议
We add an antitrust agreement to the Emergency Energy Bill.
我们打破地区性供应和经销垄断
We break up the regional supply and distribution monopolies,
就像当年对贝尔系统那样
like the Bell System.
1984年  司法部结束了贝尔公司对电话服务的垄断  将一个大公司拆分为独立小公司
那马上就会引起官司
It'll be challenged immediately in the courts.
我们不需要协议通过  只是用来吓唬人
We don't need it to pass. We just need to threaten it.
看他会不会屈服
See if he falls into line.
这事能不能低调办妥  不闹上新闻
Is there a way to do that without it making its way into the news?
我不希望世界上最有钱的有钱人
I don't want the world's wealthiest one percent
都给我打电话
on my phone sheet.
当然可以  先生
There is absolutely a way to do that, sir.
你们的酒来了
Here you go.
周二晚上就这么热闹
Crowded for a Tuesday night.
我们把室温保持在18度  而且免费
We keep it at 65 degrees. And it's free.
一杯伏特加苏打水18块也叫免费吗
If you call 18 bucks for a vodka soda free.
那也比电力公司的账单便宜
Still cheaper than a Pepco bill.
那要看你喝多少了
Depends on how many you have?
你想让我们喝醉吗
You trying to get us drunk?
你喝得越醉  给的小费越多
Drunker you are, bigger your tip.
我不用喝醉就会好好答谢优质服务
I don't have to be drunk to appreciate good service.
我去找零钱
I'll get your change.
不用了
No, you won't.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你真不要脸
You're shameless.
所以我是个好说客  干杯
Makes me a good lobbyist. Cheers.
杰姬  举动很大胆  但是没用的
So, Jackie, bold move, but it won't work.
你知道我们可以轻松通过这项修正案
You know we can pass this amendment in a heartbeat.
也许  但没有人会遵守
Maybe. But no one'll comply.
它会被推翻  最后竹篮打水一场空
It'll get overturned. Big fuss for nothing.
也许会被推翻  但依然会留下印记
It might get overturned. But it gets ink along the way.
以我对雷蒙德·塔斯克的了解
One thing I learned about Raymond Tusk
他才不在乎什么公众意见
is he doesn't two bird shits about public opinion.
他的股东们在乎
His stockholders do.
只要他一句话
They'd jump in a pit of snakes
他们就会跳进蛇窝  把自己点燃
and light themselves on fire if he gave the word.
我只是希望你能转达我们的意图
All I'm asking if that you convey our intentions.
为什么找我  弗兰克打个电话还不容易
Why me? Frank could easily pick up the phone.
你还叫他弗兰克呢
You still call him Frank?
不会当面叫  我也尽量避免见他
Not to his face, which I try to keep to a minimum.
你不觉得在白宫有个能说上话的人很好吗
Don't you appreciate having an ear in the White House?
如果真是那样还好了  但最近我净听他说了
I wouldn't, if I had an ear. But lately all I've got is a mouth.
是啊  他不是很善于倾听  对吧
Yeah. He's not the best listener, is he?
你要是为他工作就知道了
Try working for him.
你曾在他手下干过吗
You were on his staff?
八年  新闻发言人  那时你还没进入国会
Eight years. Press secretary. Before you joined Congress.
这倒说明了很多问题
That explains a lot.
比如什么
Like what?
比如很多
Like a lot.
我就当你是在羞辱我了
I'll take that as an insult.
没错
You should.
这就走吗  这就撇下我吗
That's it? You're abandoning me?
不  我去买下一轮
No. I'm buying the next round.
礼尚往来嘛
I can't accept gifts from lobbyists without reciprocating.
而且我是个好帮手
Plus, I'm a good wingman.
这样你能多跟那个酒吧女侍接触
This gets you more face time with the barmaid.
弗莱迪烧烤餐馆
你都做好了吗
You already got 'em ready?
你的手下通知我你要来了
Your guys gave me the heads-up you were coming.
希望他们没有太早吵醒你
Well, I hope that they didn't wake you earlier than usual.
操  这么热我哪能睡得着
Fuck, man. With this heat I ain't sleeping much anyway.
怎么  家里没有空调吗
What? No AC at home?
我有空调  只是不想付账单
Oh, I got a unit. I just don't want to pay the damn bill.
总的来说  这里的温度还可以
It's not too bad in here, all things considered.
那是因为我们在阴凉处
That's 'cause we in the shade.
过两小时  你要是去外面人行道上
When you get outside a couple hours from now on that pavement,
滚烫的地面能把你的鸡巴烤熟
fry your damn dick off from three feet below.
烧烤架那边一定很难熬
Must be bad over that grill.
我都觉不出区别了
I can't tell the difference no more.
但是我跟你说
I tell you what, though.
气温超过37度  这里的情况就会变糟
Stuff goes down aroundhere when the mercury pop a hundred.
之前在家里打老婆的男人会到街上来打
Man who beat his wife at home will beat her right out on the street.
把我们的兽性都暴露出来了
Brings out the animal in us.
可不是开玩笑
It ain't no joke.
以前我会被什么惊醒  枪声
What used to wake me up? Gunshots.
你知道现在是什么吗  人们操的声音
Now you know what does? People fucking.
又是呻吟又是尖叫  像巷子里的猫
Moaning and screaming like god damn cats in the alley.
俗话说得好  天热一身汗
You know what they say: When you get hot and sweaty,
脱衣就开干
it make you ripe and ready.
我喝多了
I drank too much.
我们都喝多了
We both did.
昨晚的事没发生
Last night didn't happen.
我知道
I know.
我出门之后  一切公事公办
When I walk out that door, it's business as usual.
没有特殊优待
No special treatment.
别担心  你不需要申请禁制令
Don't worry. You won't need a restraining order.
我很惊讶  你没去找那个女招待
I'm surprised you didn't go for the waitress.
你比她性感得多
You're much sexier.
得了吧
Yeah, okay.
她为小费工作  而你运作国会
She works for tips. You run Congress.
只有一半
Only half of it.
那也比她厉害得多
That's half more than she does.
那么不是我的身体吸引你
So it's not my body.
那双腿还是挺不错的
Those legs don't hurt.
你真是满口胡言
You're so full of shit.
好吧  是你的声音
Okay. It's your voice.
我的声音
My voice?
让我欲罢不能
It does something to me.
把塔斯克的意思转达给我
Let me know what Tusk has to say.
不谈公事  你还没出门呢
Business hasn't started. You haven't walked out that door yet.
看好了
Watch me.
雷米·丹顿
公事：跟雷·塔谈过了  他说法庭上见
谢谢你  杰姬
Thank you, Jackie.
我们去白宫
We're going to the White House.
小约翰在移动
Little John on the move.
我们提高赌注  把联邦能源管理委员会拉进来
We raise the bet. We get FERC involved.
调查吗
An investigation?
我们不需要国会来调用能源委员会
We don't need Congress to activate the Regulatory Commission.
但是价格听证  会耗费好几个月
But a price-fixing review? That would take months.
再说一次  只是威胁  不是真的
Again, it's the threat. Not the actuality.
他会采用同样的对策
He'll employ the same logic.
把这事拿到法庭上去
Draw it out. Fight back with appeals.
但如果联邦能源管理委员会开始行动
But he'll have to divulge his accounting
他的账目就会曝光
if FERC takes action.
没有哪个生意人愿意公开账目
Now, no businessman wants to open up his books,
尤其是430亿的账目
especially one with $43 billion.
这事开始失控了  弗兰克
This is getting outta hand, Frank.
我们不应该跟雷蒙德对着干
We shouldn't be duking it out with Raymond.
也许我们该和他谈谈
Maybe we should talk to him.
这正是他想要的  让自己回到圈里来
That's exactly what he wants. To force himself back into the mix.
把他排除在外有什么好处呢
What's to be gained by shutting him out?
给他个教训  让他知道
The simple lesson that you cannot strong-arm
他不能强迫美国总统
the president of the United States.
我们不能沦落到跟他斗气
We can't devolve to a pissing contest.
我要给雷蒙德打电话  邀他来华盛顿
I'm gonna call Raymond. Invite him to Washington.
除非你彻底投降  否则他不会接受
He won't accept anything but total surrender.
我这就打电话
I'm making the call.
别把自己逼到那个地步
Don't put yourself in that position.
我知道如何维护政府的尊严  谢谢你
I know how to maintain the integrity of my office. Thank you.
谢谢你  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
只要跟总统待两分钟
Two minutes with the president,
塔斯克就能再获青睐
and Tusk may be back in his good graces.
我要阻止他们再度联手
I need to disrupt the nuptials and prevent a second marriage.
克里斯蒂娜
Christina?
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.
拜托  你看上去棒极了
Please. You look great.
谢谢你
Thank you.
最近怎么样
How are things?
很好  琳达让我忙得脚不着地
Great. Linda works me to the bone,
但这就是我想要的
but that's what I signed up for.
据我所知  你干得很不错
Well, from what I've heard, you're doing a great job.
很高兴能听到这样的评价
Oh, that's really nice to hear.
我想跟你谈谈特莉莎
Look, I wanted to talk to you about Tricia.
你肯定注意到她仍在适应自己的角色
I'm sure you've noticed that she's still sort of adjusting to her role.
你是说自信方面吗
You mean her confidence?
我觉得你应该主动去找她谈
I think it would be great if you reached out to her.
让她知道如果有什么需要你会帮助她
Just let her know that you're there if there's anything that she needs.
我其实跟她不熟  我们见过  但是我
I don't really know her that well. I mean, we've met, but I...
没关系
That's okay.
或者就告诉她  你很喜欢为总统工作
Maybe just tell her that you enjoy working for the president
你愿意尽你所能帮助她
and you're there to be of help to her in any way you can.
-你不觉得那样有点唐突吗    -没有
- You don't think that's a little -- I don't know -- brash?   - No.
我就这么去找她
For me to just approach her like that?
不会的
No. Not at all.
《华盛顿先驱报》前雇员佐伊·巴恩斯加入头条网
杜兰特部门
罗素获得党鞭办公室支持  竞选州长
议员得到副总统支持
你已接通斯克斯基宅
You've reached the Skorsky residence.
请在哔声后留言
Leave a message after the beep.
又是汤姆·汉默施密特  还是要找简宁
Tom Hammerschmidt again. Still trying to reach Janine.
还是重要的事  谢谢
Still important. Thank you.
这是谁
汉默施密特整天都在往我们新闻处打电话
Hammerschmidt's been calling our press office all day.
我跟你一样不希望闹出任何新闻
I don't want a story to come out any more than you do.
否则我们损失一名重要线人
We lose a major asset if it does.
你能以安保理由让他噤声吗
Can you squash it for security reasons?
一旦让媒体知道就不行了  第一修正案什么的
Not once it's been shared with the press. First Amendment crap.
牢房并没能解决问题
Ward isn't making things any easier.
她想邀个大功
She wants a notch in her belt.
我们给她一个机会了
We're giving her one.
不是古德温  她想要奥尔西
Not Goodwin. She wants Orsay.
六年的首要通缉犯
Most Wanted list for six years.
我来搞定汉默施密特
I'll handle Hammerschmidt.
你得确保古德温认罪
You need to make sure Goodwin takes the plea.
35年刑期  不许假释
If 35 with no parole doesn't scare the piss out of him,
绝对能吓倒他
I don't know what will.
别去吓唬他
Then don't try to scare him.
让他彻底绝望
Remove hope from equation.
我努力控制这件事
I tried to keep this contained.
我没预料到汉默施密特会出现
I didn't anticipate Hammerschmidt.
斯克斯基女士跟他合作了吗
Is Ms. Skorsky cooperating with him?
他给她打过电话
He's called her.
我在联调局的朋友说他们没交谈过
My guy at the bureau said they haven't actually spoken.
至少没在电话里交谈过
At least not on the phone.
如果闹上法庭
If this goes to court...
不会的  先生
That won't happen, sir.
要是他发表了文章就会
It will if he publishes.
我来找你是因为我无法控制汉默施密特
I'm bringing this to you because I can't control Hammerschmidt.
我不知道该怎么做
I don't know what to do.
我们要发动正面进攻  然后守住阵线
We need to invite a full-frontal attack. Then hold the line.
你要跟他谈谈吗
You want to speak to him?
面对面  只有我们俩
Face to face. Just the two of us.
我觉得那不是个好主意  先生
I don't think that's a good idea, sir.
你有更好的主意吗
You have a better idea?
没有  先生
No, sir.
我们无法避免战争  但我们可以选择战场
We can't avoid the battle, but we can choose the battlefield.
把会面安排在白宫
Set up a meeting at the White House.
摆架子吓唬他
We'll intimidate him with formality.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President?
我知道你没有耐心听道歉
I know you don't have patience for apologies,
但我很抱歉让你失望了
but I'm sorry if I've let you down in any way.
我们集中精神解决眼前问题吧
Let's concentrate on what's in front of us.
我安排好之后会告诉你的
I'll let you know when I have a time set up.
-越快越好    -是  先生
- Soon as possible.   - Yes, sir.
这算是长篇报道的概述吗
So this is a sort of outline to the larger piece?
问题都在下一页
With questions on the next page.
我们现在是私下谈话
We're off the record.
对  私下谈话
Yes. Off the record.
汤姆  我知道你关心这个年轻人
Now, Tom, I know that you care about this young man,
我也尊重你的职业精神
and I respect you as a journalist.
但这些问题
But these questions?
你怎么不直接问我
Why don't you just ask me
为什么不再掐死别人家宠物了
when I stopped strangling people's pets.
先生  罗素议员的死
Sir, the death of Congressman Russo --
你是说我的朋友  彼得·罗素
You mean my friend, Peter Russo,
他的自杀让两个年幼的孩子失去了父亲
whose suicide left two small children with no father.
不  我不会回答关于那事的问题
No, I will not answer questions about that.
你好  我知道  不  告诉她我待会儿回电
Yes? I'm aware of that. No. Tell her I'll call her right back.
给你两分钟  刚刚是杜兰特国务卿
Two minutes. Secretary Durant.
我可以在外面等你给她回电
I can wait outside for you to call her back --
不  我们说完
No, let's finish.
那么
Now,
如果你打算发表这些内容
if you decide to print any of this,
如果你真能找到愿意发表的出版机构
assuming you find an outlet that's willing to,
那么  确实会让我头疼一阵
then, yes, it might cause me a headache for a day.
但我不会做出回应
But I will not engage.
在我看来  只会更加突出
And I think it will only prove to highlight
古德温先生的论断多么可笑  我同情他
how ridiculous Mr. Goodwin's claims are. I pity him.
真心的  我觉得他需要帮助
I truly do. I think he needs help.
我采访过很多精神异常的人  他没疯
I've interviewed many mentally ill people. He's not one of them.
我建议你把自己的文章再好好读读
Well, I would suggest that you read your own article again.
他只是非常痛苦  这两者是有区别的
He's distressed. There's a difference.
我理解  看到他入狱对你打击一定很大
Look, I understand. It must be a terrible blow to see him in prison.
但汤姆
But, Tom...
瑞秋·波斯纳确有其人
Rachel Posner exists.
我找不到她  但我已经证实她不是捏造的
I haven't been able to find her, but I've proven she's not a fantasy.
罗伊·科佩尼科也是  这些人确实存在
The same goes for Roy Kapeniak. These people were born.
他们有社保号码  既往住址...
They have social security numbers, past addresses, past --
全美各地的每个人都是如此
And so does everyone from California to Maine.
我和他们都有共谋吗
Have I conspired with all of them?
你得承认  酒驾问题确实有些解释不清的细节
You have to admit there are some troubling details regarding the DUI.
要知道  人们也是这么说51区的
You know, people say the same thing about Area 51.
有很多军事及外星人传闻的地区  美国政府对此既不肯定也不否认
你可以尽情想象
You can conjure up little gray men if you really want to.
你杀了彼得·罗素吗
Did you kill Peter Russo?
汤姆  你这就是自找没趣了
Tom, you're embarrassing yourself.
你杀了佐伊·巴恩斯吗
Did you kill Zoe Barnes?
这些荒唐事根本不值得我浪费这么多时间
I've given you more time than this nonsense deserves.
我必须得问
I have to ask these questions.
要我提问的话  我只问一句
Well, the only question I would ask is
这样的报道对古德温先生有利还是有害
does this sort of article hurt or help Mr. Goodwin?
你得做你认为对的事
You have to do what you think is -- is right.
但我希望你能理解
But I hope you can understand
我无法认真对待这些问题  有损我的身份
if I don't demean myself by taking any of it seriously.
感谢您抽出时间  副总统先生
I appreciate your time, Mr. Vice President.
怎么样
How did it go?
我的任务完成了  把这事了结了吧  道格
I did my part. Now put it to bed, Doug.
我不会允许自己再面对这样的处境
I won't submit myself to this sort of exposure again.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
塔斯克和总统见面了吗
Has Tusk met with the president yet?
琳达说他们约了四点半
Linda said they're meeting at 4:30.
联系雷米  确保他上飞机前我能见他一面
Call Remy. Make sure he doesn't get on his plane before I see him.
这就去办
I'm on it.
沃克夫人
Oh, Mrs. Walker?
我只想说  我非常荣幸
I just wanted to say how rewarding it's been,
能在白宫西楼工作
working here in the West Wing.
为您丈夫工作  我很自豪
And I'm so proud to be working for your husband.
谢谢  我知道他赏识你的勤奋
Thank you. I know he appreciates all your hard work.
既然我现在在他身边工作
Well, now that I'm working so closely with him,
如果有什么我能帮到您的
if there's anything I can do for you,
任何能帮您或他减轻负担的事...
anything that would make yours or his life easier...
继续做好你的工作就行
Just keep doing what you're doing.
我是真心的  您别客气
Truly, anything.
我想让您知道  你们可以依靠我
I want you to know you can rely on me. Both of you.
我知道  谢谢  克里斯蒂娜
I know that. Thank you, Christina.
谢谢  沃克夫人
Thanks, Mrs. Walker.
-让我来    -没事  我手不太听使唤
- Oh, here. Let me.   - Oh, it's just my hands.
-很难受吗    -是啊  今晚估计要下雨
- Are they bothering you?   - Yeah. Probably gonna get rain tonight.
我去开门
I'll get it.
不用  继续搅拌肉汤就行
Um, no. Just, uh, keep the broth moving.
我是联调局的格林特工
Agent Green, FBI.
有空吗  斯克斯基女士
Do you have a moment, Ms. Skorsky?
有  我...
Yeah. I...
我们能进去吗
May we come in?
我得把炉子关了
I just need to turn the stove off.
-待在这儿  妈妈    -是谁
- Stay in here, Mom.   - Who is it?
待在这儿就是了
Just stay in here.
只有那一次吗
Only that once?
之后我就没见过他了  也没回他电话
And I haven't seen him since, or returned his calls.
他几次试图联系你
How many times has he tried to call you?
我不知道  大概八九次吧
I don't know. Eight or nine times, maybe.
之后他消停了一段时间
And then he stopped after a while.
他提到过机器人希洛尼摩斯或嘉文·奥尔西吗
Did he mention anything about Hieronymus Bot or Gavin Orsay?
我觉得我该找个律师来
You know, I think I should talk to a lawyer.
现在我们并不怀疑你是同谋
Right now you're not suspected of being an accomplice.
如果你找律师  那我们就要考虑一下了
If you call a lawyer, we might have to reconsider.
-他提到了个黑客    -希洛尼摩斯
- He mentioned some hacker.   - Hieronymus.
我告诉他  联系那个人不是什么好主意
I told him I thought it was a bad idea to contact him.
你知道他所持的论调吗
Are you aware of what he's claiming?
不
No.
你本来在跟他合作
That you and he were working together.
你相信他那套阴谋论
That you believe in this conspiracy theory.
是你收到了巴恩斯女士的私密照片
That it was you who received explicit photos of Ms. Barnes.
这些都是真的吧
Is any of that true?
你得跟我们回华盛顿
We need you to come back to D.C. with us
在联邦检察官的见证下签署这份声明
and sign this statement in the presence of the U.S. attorney.
-你们想让我指证他说谎吗    -他没有吗
- You want me to call him a liar.   - Isn't he?
我不能这样对他
I can't do that to him.
你还得和汤姆·汉默施密特谈谈
We also need you to speak with Tom Hammerschmidt.
求求你们  能别把我扯进来吗
You know what? Please, can you just keep me out of this?
我和那个黑客毫无瓜葛...
I had nothing to do with the hacker or the...
斯克斯基女士  我们愿意相信你
Ms. Skorsky, we want to believe you,
你写下来我们就相信你
and we will if you put all of it in writing.
他没犯罪  你们查错人了
He's not a criminal. You're going after the wrong person.
如果你们认为你们能吓唬我
And if you think that you can intimidate me,
在我自己家这样骚扰我
harass me like this in my own home,
我会提出正式投诉
I will file a formal complaint.
你语气越来越像他了
You're starting to sound an awful lot like him.
你们不能逮捕我  我什么都没做
You can't arrest me. I haven't done anything.
你们快走
I'd like you to leave.
我有权请律师  而且你们没有逮捕令
I have a right to legal counsel, and you haven't presented a warrant.
我们可以逮捕你  斯克斯基女士
We can arrest you, Ms. Skorsky,
以教唆网络恐怖主义的名义
for abetting an act of cyber terrorism.
如果你接下来三年都耗在法庭里
Who's going to take care of your mother while you're
谁来照顾你母亲呢
spending the next three years in courtrooms?
麻烦您抬手
Would you please raise your arms?
-密查姆就不用了    -先生
- No, Meechum.   - Sir...
密查姆  我知道你不想跟我握手
Meechum. I know you don't want to shake my hand,
我们就直接略过吧
so we'll just skip that part.
总统完全没有提
The president didn't mention anything about it.
他为什么要提  抓你个冷不丁更好
Why would he? The better to catch you off-guard.
那你为什么要提
Then why would you?
好避免不必要的冲突
So we can avoid unnecessary conflict.
加勒特可不会撒谎
Garrett's not a good liar.
真正会说谎的人总是让人觉得
The gift of a good liar is making people think
他天生不会说谎
you lack a talent for lying.
我远比你了解他
I know him far better than you
我知道他天生会什么  不会什么
and so I know what talents he has and lacks.
但假设他确实说谎了
But let's assume he did lie.
我不担心联邦能源监管委员会的调查
I'm not intimidated by a FERC investigation.
听证会还没开始
You'd have grid overload and brown-outs
就会出现电网过载  灯火管制
before you could even get a hearing.
你在蓄意抬高电价
You are deliberately keeping electric prices at inflated rates,
这是违法的
which is illegal.
不  这是对自由市场的反应
No. I'm responding to free market.
是受监管的自由市场
A regulated free market.
你为什么这么做  弗兰克
Why are you doing this, Frank?
雷米也这样问过我
Remy asked me the same thing.
你这是故意找我茬
You're making this about me.
不是针对你  雷蒙德
This isn't personal, Raymond.
能源市场的健全是我唯一在乎的
The integrity of our energy markets is my only concern.
你当然是针对我
Of course it's personal.
我让你说服加勒特不再与中国针锋相对
I asked you personally to convince Garrett to pull back from China.
而你偏偏跟我对着干
You personally chose not to.
你还故意破坏峰会
You personally sabotaged the summit.
我政治生涯中从未
I have never once in my political career
你还让内阁把我逼上绝路
And you personally advised the cabinet to push me up against the wall.
因私人感情而耽误正事
allow personal feelings to get in the way of pragmatic --
别跟我耍花招  弗兰克  我耍不动了
Do not try and spin me, Frank. I am too old to tango.
那我就直说了
Then I'll be blunt.
接受核能补助
Accept the subsidies
否则就面对能源委员会
or deal with FERC.
没有第三条路可选
There is no third way here.
你是故意想毁掉总统吗
Are you intentionally trying to destroy the president?
我是想保护总统  免受你的伤害
I'm trying to protect the president. From you.
你是在为国务卿提名的事报复我吧
This is about the secretary of state nomination, isn't it?
我现在是副总统了  雷蒙德
I'm the vice president now, Raymond.
我不会为陈年往事掉泪
I don't cry over what happened in kindergarten.
我力保你  你才当上副总统
You're vice president because I vouched for you.
因为你别无选择
Because you had no other options.
这是政治需要
Political necessity.
给你24小时做决定
You have 24 hours to decide.
不用送了
I'll show myself out.
你好
Hello.
雷蒙德  这是克莱尔
Raymond, this is Claire.
安德伍德夫人  见到你很荣幸
Mrs. Underwood, it is an honor.
我妻子珍  很欣赏你最近做出的种种努力
Jean-- my wife-- has been very taken with your recent efforts.
改天我一定要见见她
Well, I'd like to meet her one day.
我相信她肯定非常愿意
She would very much like that, I'm sure.
那你怎么看呢
And what about you?
什么意思
I'm sorry?
我们最近在做的事  你怎么看呢
What are your thoughts about our recent efforts?
防止不必要的暴力
Oh. I am in favor of anything
我当然支持
that prevents unnecessary violence.
很高兴见到你  安德伍德夫人
It's nice to meet you, Mrs. Underwood.
祝你今晚开球好运  副总统先生
And, good luck with that first pitch tonight, Mr. Vice President.
这次要投进本垒板  夫人再见
Make it to the plate this time. Ma'am.
这防弹背心真不舒服
This Kevlar is cooking me.
必须得穿  先生
We have to use it, sir.
我练习时没穿过  这下胳膊都转不动了
Well, I didn't practice with it, and now I can hardly rotate my arm.
我该提醒您的  对不起
I should have mentioned it. I apologize.
这球要是过不了本垒板  我拿你是问
If this ball doesn't make it over the plate, it's your ass.
你在这儿干什么  没事可做吗
And what are you doing here? Don't you have things to do?
我没来过卡姆登球场
Never been to Camden Yards.
女士们先生们  马上将投出今晚第一球
Ladies and gentlemen, here to throw out the first pitch tonight,
我们有幸请上  美国副总统
we are honored to introduce the vice president of the United States,
弗兰克·安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
先生  密查姆的球
Boss, boss. Meechum's ball.
非常感谢  吉祥物呢
Thank you very much. Where's the mascot?
唱得真好
Beautifully done.
晚上好
Good evening.
今晚很热  大家都想赶快看比赛
Now I know it's a hot night and you all want to get to the baseball.
所以我一投出这玩意儿
So as soon as I throw this sucker,
大家就喝点东西  享受比赛
grab a drink, enjoy the game,
祝两队好运
and best of luck to both teams.
我收回那句话  这是在卡姆登球场啊
Scratch that. We're at Camden Yards.
金莺队加油
Go Orioles!
快走  快走
Go, go!
据说是控制节点的
I'm told the distribution line that controls
配电线路造成了供电中断
the pinch point caused the outages.
贝科  你的一家公司
BAPCO. One of your companies.
是的  电量出问题了
Yes, sir. There was a capacity issue.
我的人在以最快速度抢修
We're working as quickly as we can to resolve it.
有三位州长给我打过电话了
Well, I've got three governors calling.
医院在用应急电源  你们最好尽快修理
Hospitals on emergency power. So quickly better mean quickly.
最快也要2到3个小时  也许能快些
The latest estimate I got was two to three hours, maybe sooner.
雷蒙德  这是故意的吗
Raymond, was this intentional?
先生  我知道你最近不怎待见我
Sir, I know you don't hold me in the highest regard at the moment.
但是你居然会这么想  我很吃惊
But I am alarmed that you could even entertain such a thought.
但这时候出现这种事让人很难相信是巧合
Yeah, well, the timing makes coincidence hard to swallow.
是热浪的缘故  热浪会让电网达到使用极限
There is a heat wave. That always pushes the grid to its limits.
好吧  快让人们摆脱黑暗
All right, let's get the people out of the dark.
每30分钟报告一次进展情况
Updates every 30 minutes on your progress.
先生  我要通知你  我明天可能要
I should inform you, sir, that I may need to take
关闭两座电厂做不定期维修
two of my plants offline tomorrow for unscheduled maintenance.
什么  哪两座厂
Why? Which ones?
佐治亚州和田纳西州
Georgia and Tennessee.
这次停电使这两座厂的负荷很大
This blackout has put a great deal of stress on them.
我的工程师们担心燃料棒密封条破损
My engineers are concerned about the seals on the fuel rods.
那么东南部也要断电吗
So we're looking at outages on the southeast grid, too?
有可能  几天吧
Could be. For a few days.
这绝对不行
No, that's unacceptable.
安全第一   我们不希望出事故
Safety comes first. We don't want an accident.
好吧  详细情况报告给琳达  尽快
All right, let's get a full report to Linda, ASAP.
是  先生  谢谢你
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
他在耍花招
He's toying with you.
不  或许真有这样的安全问题
No, this could be a legitimate safety issue.
他想夺回权力  那几个电厂没事
He wants a seat back at the table. Those plants are fine.
他为什么这么做  我们的确有分歧
Why is he doing this? We've had our differences,
但非要做出这么偏激的事吗
but something drastic like this?
我跟他说了能源委员会可能会展开听证会
Well, I did tell him about the possible FERC action.
什么
You did what?
他打电话给我  我接了电话
Well, he called me. I answered the call.
你怎么不立即通知我
Why didn't you inform me immediately?
他说你们的谈话很有成效
He told me you had a productive talk.
他同意核能补助的事  我以为你们谈妥了
That he was on board with the subsidy. I assumed everything was fine.
他提议进行新一轮贸易谈判
He was proposing renewed trade talks.
我们根本没谈核能补助的事
We didn't talk about the subsidy at all.
他把我们俩都给耍了
He's playing both of us then.
如果他说他同意了
If he told you he was on board,
你为什么还提能源委员会的事呢
why'd you bring up FERC?
我说这下我放心了
I told him I was relieved.
要是他不答应  我们可要采取行动了
That we could have taken action if he didn't comply.
你觉得他是在套你的话吗
You think he's fishing?
想套出我们下一步行动
To see what our next move might be?
就是这样  先生
I think so, sir. I mean,
南部两个发电厂的事他在说谎
he is lying about those two plants in the south.
我们不能猜测  一定要确定
Well, we can't guess. We have to be certain.
你想让雷蒙德·塔斯克来做风险评估
Well, do you want Raymond Tusk to assess that risk?
还是政府来做
Or the United States government?
你是说我们接管他的电厂吗
Are you suggesting we take over his facilities?
有过这样的先例
There is precedent there.
伍德罗·威尔逊接管铁路三年整
Woodrow Wilson did it with the railroads for three full years.
那是战争时期
In a time of war.
是在危急时期  就像现在这样
In a time of emergency, which is what this is.
人民需要一位领袖  总统先生
The country needs a leader, Mr. President.
满足他们  别向雷蒙德·塔斯克屈服
Give them one. Do not bend to Raymond Tusk.
看完了
I'm done.
我说过你可能不喜欢
I said you might not like it.
这让我看起来像是疯了
It makes me seem crazy.
这是最收敛的版本了
This is the most toned-down version.
我尽力用最和善的口吻  不掺入偏见
I tried to be as kind as I could without being biased.
你不希望这报道公诸于众吧
I don't think you want this going out into the world.
我能和简宁谈谈吗
Can I talk to Janine?
让他走
Tell him to go.
他想让你离开
He wants you to leave.
-你说了谎    -卢卡斯
- You lied.   - Lucas...
你骗了汤姆  也骗了联邦检察官
You lied to Tom. You lied to the U.S. Attorney.
-我不知道还能怎么办    -说真话
- I didn't know what else to do.   - Tell the truth.
他们会逮捕我  他们会让我失去信誉
They'll arrest me. They'll discredit everything I say.
到时  人们会像不相信你那样不相信我
And nobody is going to believe me more than they believe you.
但我们能让公众知道  让人们产生疑问
But we can get the story out there. Get people asking questions.
不  他们只会觉得我们俩都疯了
No. It'll just look like two crazy instead of one.
所以你打算自保
So you're saving yourself.
我想保护我们两个人
I'm trying to save the both of us.
拜托了
Please.
认罪吧
Take the plea.
-我是无罪的    -你不是
- I'm not guilty.   - You are.
你犯了罪
You committed a crime.
-罪名还不只一项    -但不包括谋杀
- Multiple crimes.   - Not murder.
承认罪行  好好表现  早点出来
Take the plea. Be good. Get out early.
所有人都坑我
Everybody -- everybody's fucked me.
如果我是想害你  就不会来了
If I was trying to fuck you I wouldn't be here.
他要逃脱罪责了  是吗
He's gonna get away with it, isn't he?
是的
Yes, he is.
-有加冰的茶吗  给我一杯    -没有
- Take an iced tea if you have any.   - We don't.
我真不想总这样偷偷摸摸的
I wish I didn't have to keep coming through back doors like this.
这不是不想让新闻界的朋友
Well, we wouldn't want our friends in the fourth estate
知道你来这里嘛
to know you were here, would we?
特别是你费了好大的功夫
Especially since you've gone to such lengths
一直置身政治斗争之外
to remain above the fray of politics.
你不能夺走发电厂  弗兰克
You can't seize the plants, Frank.
我们还没得手呢
We haven't seized anything yet.
我们有这准备  但只要你合作就不会那样
We're ready to, but we won't if you cooperate.
这是违法的
It's illegal.
并不违法  你心里清楚
It's not. You know that.
紧急情况下  总统可以下达行政命令
The president can issue an executive order in times of emergency.
我会在法庭上据理力争
I'll fight it in court.
那比能源委员会的调查更费时
Which will take even longer than a FERC investigation would.
而在此期间  你的发电厂无法盈利
And in the meantime, you make nothing from those plants.
我们说好的
We agreed.
就在这里  我们达成了协议
Right here in this room, we agreed to work together.
做出了合作的承诺
We agreed as men of our word.
我一直信守承诺
And I held up my end of that bargain
可你在法案的事上背信弃义
until you abandoned me on the bill.
我让雷米去协助你了
I sent Remy to help you.
那是法案通过参议院之后  你之前可没帮忙
After I got it passed through the Senate with no help from you.
我不能和总统闹僵
I had to protect my relationship with the president.
斯波特瑟尔韦尼亚峰会期间
And then you tried to use me
你还企图利用我
during the summit in Spotsylvania.
我活着不是为了做你最好的朋友
I was not put on this earth to be your best friend
也不是为了和你分享我的所有情报
or to share every piece of information I have with you.
我们只是达成了互利共赢的合作关系
We agreed to a mutually beneficial partnership. That's all.
是的  而我现在发现
Yes. And what's become very clear to me
跟你合作对我没有任何好处
is that I benefit in no way from this partnership.
我们就不装傻了
Let's not pretend to be naive.
我们最看重的都是个人利益
We both respect self-interest above all else.
现在  双方利益不再一致
Our versions of that no longer align.
你就要犯下无法挽回的错误了
You are on the verge of making an irreversible mistake,
副总统先生
Mr. Vice President.
我的确可能是在犯错  谁知道呢
I may well be making a mistake. Who knows?
我只知道你会联系琳达
What I do know is that you'll be calling Linda
告诉她你接受核能补助
and telling her that you'll accept the subsidies.
你有钱  雷蒙德
You may have all the money, Raymond,
但我有权
but I have all the men with guns.
这是设好号码的一次性电话  她在等你答复
It's a burner, pre-dialed. She's expecting.
对了  这是昨晚的
Oh, and, uh, yes. From last night.
按行话说  现在轮到你发球了
The ball's in your court, as they say.
上帝  你吓死我了
Oh, Jesus Christ. You scared the shit outta me.
你就这么随随便便地喊上帝吗
Are you supposed to take the lord's name in vain like that?
继续开着
Leave it on.
电费太贵
It costs too much.
我会付的
I'll take care of it.
古德温认罪了  他要进监狱了
Goodwin took the plea. He's going away.
所以一切都结束了吗
So does that mean this is all over?
没有  我们还是要小心
No. We still have to be careful.
为什么  没有他  就不会有人找我了吧
But why? If he's gone, then nobody's looking for me, right?
据我们所知没有
Not that we know of.
在确保万无一失之前  一切照常
Until we know, nothing changes.
那你来就是为了让我空欢喜一场吗
So what, you just came over here to get my hopes up?
我来是为了确保你今晚不去教堂
I came here to make sure that you don't go to church tonight.
你想干我吗
Do you want to fuck me?
-这才是你的本意吧    -不是
- Is that what this is all about?   - No.
你以前干过我
You've done it before.
那不一样
That was different.
够了
Stop it.
我一向能察觉男人对我的欲望
If there's one thing I know, it's when a man wants me.
我在教会得知了拉结的故事
I learned who Rachel was in church.
拉结是《圣经》中和瑞秋同名的女子
她年轻漂亮
She was young and beautiful.
雅各在她照看羊喝水时爱上了她
Jacob fell in love with her while she was watering a lamb.
他做了七年的工
And she became his wife after he worked seven years
才终于娶到她
to earn her hand in marriage.
拉结有个叫约瑟的儿子
Rachel had one son. Joseph.
后来他成了国王
He became a king.
你饿不饿
Are you hungry?
■
这一集中  能源大亨塔斯克用"拉闸限电"的手段来要挟总统
现实中美国的能源巨头可不敢如此嚣张
现实中美国联邦政府对能源公司的监管是相当严格的
能源部对企业的日常运营有诸多法规限制
一旦出现事故  造成污染
公司会受司法部的调查  起诉  承担严重后果
2010年4月  英国石油公司钻井平台发生事故
造成墨西哥湾严重污染  美国司法部的调查至今仍未结束
除了多名直接责任人被起诉
英国石油公司截止目前已经在多宗诉讼中赔偿了422亿美元
■
美国作为世界上最大的能源消耗国  如何解决长期的能源供应
同时兼顾环境保护  一直是两党的争论焦点
共和党在能源问题上主张充分利用美国的石油资源
放松对传统能源行业的监管
民主党则推崇绿色可再生能源
同时通过立法监管对石油和煤炭企业严加限制
过去几年中  由于美国发现了大量的页岩气储备
同时开采技术有了新的突破  渴望在2020年实现"北美能源独立"
不再依靠北美以外地区的能源进口
所以在页岩气价格迅速下降的背景下
奥巴马政府主张在能源上采取"百花齐放"的政策
在推动新型能源的同时  也鼓励传统能源的发展
但是由于民主党左派一味强调环境和气候变化问题
美国传统能源行业普遍认为现政府的政策极大地束缚了行业的发展
■
由于两党在能源问题上立场相左
所以现实中的塔斯克这样的能源巨头非常注意本行业的公共形象
如果有"拉闸限电"这样的事情发生  不仅涉及的公司会被调查
在民怨沸腾的情况下  国会也极可能迅速介入
通过立法手段对整个行业加强监管